blitwise.com 2018-12-25

# BlitWise Productions, Shareware & Free Games

**Online Privacy Policy of BlitWise Productions LLC**

This document sets forth the Online Privacy Policy (the "Policy") of BlitWise Productions LLC ("BlitWise"). This Policy describes the ways we collect, store, use, and manage the information, including personally identifiable information, that you provide or we collect in connection with our websites, including www.BlitWise.com (the "Site") or any BlitWise game or software provided on any platform (Apple's iOS App Store, Google Play, our own site, etc) (collectively, the "Service"). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Service. This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities or the collection of information other than through the Site. Your use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and consent to the terms herein.

BlitWise is committed to safeguarding the privacy of Users of the Service. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you provide us remains private and is used only for the purposes set forth herein. Additionally, in no event will BlitWise sell customer lists or profiles to outside sources.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

All "personal information" ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, examples being names, street addresses, email address, billing address, credit card number and expiration dates) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. BlitWise reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion.

Please note that if BlitWise sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or BlitWise (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by, or merged with, another entity, BlitWise may provide to such entity customer and personal information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without your consent.

**Third Parties**

The Service contains links to other sites or services at which personal information is collected. If you access such sites or services, the collection and use of your personal information will not be governed by this Privacy Policy but by the privacy policy applicable to that service, unless expressly provided to the contrary. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information. Because BlitWise does not control the privacy practices of third parties you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of those third parties. When you link to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of that website. We encourage you to ask questions and review the applicable privacy policy before you disclose your personal information to third parties. We do not try to control, and disclaim responsibility for, information provided by other Users or third parties that is made available through our Service. Such information may contain errors, intentional or otherwise, or may be inappropriate or inaccurate and in some cases will be mislabeled.

**Collection of personal information**

As a User of our Service, You can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as requesting information, downloading games, or participating in the forum discussions, BlitWise may ask You to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting a form. It is completely optional for You to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, BlitWise may ask that You provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, company name, mailing address (including ZIP code), email address, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask You to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If You do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, You will not be able to engage in that activity.

When You use the Service, BlitWise or third parties authorized by BlitWise, may also collect certain technical and routing information about your computer or mobile device to facilitate your use of the Site and its services. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, the Internet Protocol ("IP") address of your computer, unique device ID, hardware type, media access control ("MAC") address, or device name. We use these environmental variables to facilitate and track your use of the Site and its services. BlitWise also uses such environmental variables for troubleshooting and to measure usage patterns of the Service. Without expressly informing You, we do not match such information with any of your personal information.

When you use the Service, your BlitWise identification or avatar may be visible to the public depending upon the nature of the Service You use. You may use a variety of identities without revealing your primary identification by creating an avatar or alias. An avatar consists of a name and some information that you show in a profile to other users on BlitWise. When creating such profile please be mindful that such information is available to all online.

When You submit personal information to BlitWise through this Service, You understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which BlitWise and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices, including, without limitation, the United States of America. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, authorized vendors of BlitWise may undertake the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information. Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties. One instance where this could occur is in conjunction with framed pages in which the URL for the pages is not visible and the pages are being hosted by a vendor of BlitWise.

**Authentication and Push Notifications**

If You choose to sign up for an account for any part of BlitWise's Service using a third party (such as Twitter, Facebook, etc.), BlitWise may use that party's oAuth authentication information. This may include a unique oAuth token, a Facebook user number, or Twitter account name. BlitWise will not have access to your account password, and will not communicate information to Third Party servers except communication with user configured services such as Facebook and Twitter as outlined in this Policy.

Some parts of the Service may seek to send Push notifications to your device. When activating, your device may ask permission to send you notifications. If You refuse, no further information will be taken for purposes of notification. If you agree, we will register You on our servers to receive notifications. When registering for notifications, some identification is collected from your client. This may include an anonymous device identifier, your username, and a client push notification identifier (provided by your device OS, including but not limited to Apple, Windows, or Android). 

Notifications may be processed through a contracted service provider, such as Parse. When You receive a notification, it may be processed through their servers, as well as the servers for your device's push notifications (such as Apple's iOS APS)

Parse may monitor the feedback servers dedicated to your device through Apple, etc. If You uninstall a BlitWise product, they will remove your account information from our database in a timely fashion.

**Policies For Children**

BlitWise does not knowingly collect or use any personal information from Users under 13 years of age without express parental consent pursuant to the Children's On-line Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (hereinafter COPPA). Once verifiable parental consent is obtained by BlitWise, the personal information is treated no differently than adult users, in that in no event will BlitWise sell customer lists or profiles.

Pursuant to COPPA, prior to submitting verifiable parental consent the parents of children under 13 years of age have the right to receive information describing the specific types of personal information to be collected by the site. Additionally, a parent has the right at any time to refuse to permit (1) the operator's further use or maintenance of the child's personal information in retrievable form, and/or (2) further online collection of personal information from that child.

BlitWise has the ability to terminate service, pursuant to COPPA to a child whose parent has refused to permit the operator's further use or maintenance in retrievable form, or future online collection of personal information from such child.

Finally, BlitWise will not condition a child's participation in a game, offering of a prize, or any other activity upon the child disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in such activity.

**Use of Personal Information**

BlitWise collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. For example, if you subscribe to a forum or download a game, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered Users. Your personal information is also used to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of BlitWise and selected third parties if You have so opted to receive such communications.

Rights and benefits mentioned above for which we may use your personal information may include, but are not limited to:

Creation of accounts, identifying connections with other BlitWise users when prompted by You, operating and improving the Service, communicating with You regarding promotions, updates, and other BlitWise offers, delivering products you request and/or purchase, responding to questions, providing customer and technical assistance, and sending You confirmations, updates, invoices, alerts, and other user authorized communications.

BlitWise may collect information about the use of the Service, such as the types of services used and how many Users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any User individually. BlitWise may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

BlitWise will comply with all local and international law. We may release your information as permitted or required by law, and to enforce or apply our rights. This may include protecting the rights and safety of our users and exchange of information with other organizations for purposes of preventing fraud.

**If You Do Not Wish to Disclose User Information**

If You do not want to provide us with certain User Information then You may opt out by not using the Service that provides us with such User Information.

**Terms of Service**

When You use the BlitWise Service, you are subject to the BlitWise Terms of Service.

**How do I contact BlitWise?**

If You have questions concerning BlitWise's Privacy Policy You may contact BlitWise at Post Office Box 5723, Endicott, New York 13763, and/or [techsupport@blitwise.com](mailto:techsupport@blitwise.com).

**Updating Personal Information and Privacy Preferences**

You may also change or correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether You wish to receive promotional communications from BlitWise or third parties) at any time by writing to BlitWise at the contact information posted above.

Please include your name, address, and/or email address when you contact us. No specific form is required to notify BlitWise of changes to your address or privacy preferences.

**Privacy-Related Inquiries and Complaints**

As a family friendly Service, BlitWise takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that BlitWise has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information or You have other related inquiries or concerns, You may write to the BlitWise technical support employee at the address indicated above.

In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible, the nature of your inquiry or the ways in which You believe that the BlitWise Online Privacy Policy has been violated. We will investigate your inquiry or complaint promptly. Please note that if You provide BlitWise with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact You with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), BlitWise cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored. Also, please note that BlitWise is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-BlitWise websites to which this Site or any other BlitWise Service may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.
